Guide to the New York Produce Exchange Records 1860-1955 MS 449
New-York Historical Society
New York Produce Exchange records
1860-1955
New-York Historical Society
New York Produce Exchange
MS 449
62 Linear feet in 330 volumes and 1 box
The collection includes the records of the New York Produce Exchange and the related New York Commercial Association, spanning the years 1860-1955. Holding 330 volumes and some unbound papers, there are records of meeting minutes of the Board of Managers, members, and committees; arbitration proceedings and resolutions; membership; data on daily trades, calls, and quotations for a wide range of commodities including cotton seed oil, wheat and other grains, and many more; accounting ledgers and journals; and some employee payroll records. Buildings Committee records relate to the George Post-designed building that opened in 1884 on Broadway at Bowling Green.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Arrangement
The collection is comprised almost entirely of 330 volumes, which are presented first in the finding aid container list. These are followed by the content of one box of unbound documents.
The volumes are presented in the finding aid in the order of their "sequence number" (SN). The sequence numbers simply represent the order that the volumes were stored on the shelves at N-YHS. The numbers were assigned to the volumes in early 2020 in preparation for offsite storage. Generally, volumes of related content were together on the shelves, but there are inconsistencies. There are also inconsistencies in the sequence in terms of chronological order of the volumes.
Biographical / Historical
The New York Produce Exchange, which dissolved in 1973, traced its origin to the 1840s-1850s and the informal association of merchants that engaged in the trade or exchange of various commodities in New York City. In the late 1850s, in response to the merchants' desire to acquire a building for a suitable place to conduct trade, subscriptions were raised and a building constructed and opened for business in 1861. That same year a company—the New York Produce Exchange Company—was incorporated, apparently with responsibility for the physical plant and overall administration of Exchange operations, but not for regulation of the commodities markets and the tenants, who were the merchants themselves. The merchants retained that self-regulatory responsibility and, on April 19, 1862, they incorporated as the New-York Commercial Association. The two organizations continued to operate in parallel until perhaps 1872. In 1868 the Association had its charter amended and changed its name to New York Produce Exchange and in 1872 the corporation took ownership of the building, completing the unification of the business and building forms of the Exchange. (It is not clear whether the two corporations actually merged at some point or whether the original Company of 1861 eventually dissolved after the sale of the building.)
Through the 1870s, space for the growing activities of the Exchange was a pressing problem; this was resolved with the construction of a large building, designed by George Post, at Bowling Green in 1884. The Exchange remained there until 1957 when it moved to new quarters and the 1884 building was demolished.
Over the course of a century, the specific commodities that the Produce Exchange engaged in varied. Grains (e.g. wheat) and cotton seed oil (commonly abbreviated in the records as "CSO") were major products for much or all of its history, but other commodities were also traded, including tallow, pork, petroleum, lard, and others. Initially a cash or spot market only (i.e., for immediate delivery of goods), the Exchange also participated in the futures market (i.e., contracts for future delivery of commodities on agreed terms).
Well beyond simply providing a setting for the trading of goods, the Produce Exchange, as with exchanges generally, was a fundamental element of free market capitalism and the effort to keep economic power, by shaping the market, within the hands of the merchants. Accordingly, the Produce Exchange maintained various committees for admitting members, arbitrating disputes, inspecting the quality of goods, setting rules for deliveries of commodities, and other self-regulating and self-disciplining devices that would serve the interests of the merchants as a class, while also serving as justifications for minimal or no interventions by the legislature or courts, and for the homogenization of products by farmers and other producers.
(Sources include: E.R. Carhart, "The New York Produce Exchange" in "The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science" of September 1911, available at https://www.jstor.org/stable/pdf/1011641.pdf; and various New York Times articles.)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the New York Produce Exchange, 1974.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes the records of the New York Produce Exchange and the related New York Commercial Association, spanning the years 1860-1955, which includes all but the last couple of decades of the organization's history. The collection consists almost entirely of 330 volumes of records: minutes of meetings of the Board of Managers, members, and committees; records of complaints, arbitration proceedings, and dispute resolution agreements; membership registers and dues payment records; data on daily trades, calls, and quotations for a wide range of commodities including cotton seed oil (CSO), wheat and other grains, black pepper, and many more; accounting ledgers and journals for the Exchange's General Fund and special funds, such as the Chemists Fund; and some employee payroll records. Committee records include those of the Buildings Committee responsible for oversight of construction of the building that opened in 1884 on Broadway at Bowling Green. A set of boxed unbound papers document the Exchange's negotiations with the federal government's Arbitration Committee in 1928-1929 concerning delivery contracts for cotton seed oil.
Arbitration agreements, Commercial -- New York (State) -- New York.; Commodity exchanges -- New York (State) -- New York.; Prices.; Produce trade.; Account books.; Journals (accounts); Membership lists.; Minutes (administrative records); Payroll records.; New York Commercial Association -- Archives.; New York Produce Exchange -- Archives.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 1, 1866-1873 (Offsite-box PE-1, Volume SN-1)
  Scope and Contents
  The first two volumes of the Complaint Committee are labeled on the spine as "minutes," the next two are labeled as "proceedings," volumes 6-19 are labeled as "records of the complaint committee," and volumes after that are labeled "record of complaints," though many volumes have lost their spine/labeling. The word "record" is used in this container list to link these volumes together.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 2, 1873 (Offsite-box PE-1, Volume SN-2)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 3. February-November 1874 (Offsite-box PE-1, Volume SN-3)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 4. November 1874-November 1875, 1874-1875 (Offsite-box PE-1, Volume SN-4)
  There is no following volume 5 in the collection.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 6. May 1876-February 1877, 1876-1877 (Offsite-box PE-1, Volume SN-5)
  There is no preceding Volume 5 of the Complaints Committee in the collection.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 7. February-November 1877 (Offsite-box PE-2, Volume SN-6)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 8. November 1877-March 1878, 1877-1878 (Offsite-box PE-2, Volume SN-7)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 9. March-October 1878 (Offsite-box PE-2, Volume SN-8)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 10. October 1878-October 1879, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box PE-2, Volume SN-9)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 11. October 1879-October 1880, 1879-1880 (Offsite-box PE-2, Volume SN-10)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 12. October 1880-August 1881, 1880-1881 (Offsite-box PE-3, Volume SN-11)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 13. September 1881-August 1882, 1881-1882 (Offsite-box PE-3, Volume SN-12)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 14. August 1882-January 1883, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box PE-3, Volume SN-13)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 15. February-August 1883 (Offsite-box PE-3, Volume SN-14)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 16. August 1883-January 1884, 1883-1884 (Offsite-box PE-3, Volume SN-15)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 17. January-September 1884 (Offsite-box PE-4, Volume SN-16)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 18. September 1884-March 1885, 1884-1885 (Offsite-box PE-4, Volume SN-17)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 19. March-December 1885 (Offsite-box PE-4, Volume SN-18)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 20. December 1885-August 1886, 1885-1886 (Offsite-box PE-4, Volume SN-19)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 21. August 1886-June 1887, 1886-1887 (Offsite-box PE-4, Volume SN-20)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 22. June 1887-December 1888, 1887-1888 (Offsite-box PE-5, Volume SN-21)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 23. December 1888-April 1890, 1888-1890 (Offsite-box PE-5, Volume SN-22)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 24. May 1890-September 1891, 1890-1891 (Offsite-box PE-5, Volume SN-23)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 25. September 1891-November 1892, 1891-1892 (Offsite-box PE-5, Volume SN-24)
  See SN-32 for the following volume 26.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 27. November 1893-January 1895, 1893-1895 (Offsite-box PE-6, Volume SN-25)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 28. February 1895-March 1897, 1895-1897 (Offsite-box PE-6, Volume SN-26)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 29. March 1897-November 1898, 1897-1898 (Offsite-box PE-7, Volume SN-27)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 30. November 1898-August 1900, 1898-1900 (Offsite-box PE-7, Volume SN-28)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 31. September 1900-October 1901, 1900-1901 (Offsite-box PE-8, Volume SN-29)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 32. November 1901-February 1903, 1901-1903 (Offsite-box PE-8, Volume SN-30)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 33. February 1903-September 1904, 1903-1904 (Offsite-box PE-8, Volume SN-31)
  See SN-39 for the following volume 34.
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 26. November 1892-October 1893, 1892-1893 (Offsite-box PE-9, Volume SN-32)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 35. July 1906-November 1907, 1906-1907 (Offsite-box PE-9, Volume SN-33)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 36. November 1907-May 1909, 1907-1909 (Offsite-box PE-9, Volume SN-34)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 37. June 1909-September 1912, 1909-1912 (Offsite-box PE-10, Volume SN-35)
- Board and Complaint Committee notices. March 1923-August 1931, 1923-1931 (Offsite-box PE-10, Volume SN-36)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 38. September 1912-June 1915, 1912-1915 (Offsite-box PE-11, Volume SN-37)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 39. June 1915-June 1918, 1915-1918 (Offsite-box PE-11, Volume SN-38)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 34. November 1904-August 1906, 1904-1906 (Offsite-box PE-12, Volume SN-39)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 40. June 1918-November 1921, 1918-1921 (Offsite-box PE-12, Volume SN-40)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 42. July 1926-April 1936, 1926-1936 (Offsite-box PE-13, Volume SN-41)
- Complaint Committee records, Volume 41. November 1921-July 1926, 1921-1926 (Offsite-box PE-14, Volume SN-42)
- Arbitration Committee records. Bond book. July 1861-March 1867, 1861-1867 (Offsite-box PE-15, Volume SN-43)
  The Arbitration Committee volumes (SN-43 to SN-70 and SN-331) include minutes, agreements, bonds, awards, and other records, though it was not always clear to the archivist which specific types were in each volume. It is possible/likely that the Exchange used terms interchangeably over the decades. Accordingly the generic term "records" is used in this container list. Where it appears that a more specific document type is in the volume, that is noted. Otherwise, most of the volumes appear to include minutes and agreements.
- Arbitration Committee records. Bond book. April 1867-June 1868, 1867-1868 (Offsite-box PE-15, Volume SN-44)
- Arbitration Committee records. July 1861-May 1868, 1861-1868 (Offsite-box PE-15, Volume SN-45)
- Arbitration Committee records. June 1872-October 1874, 1872-1874 (Offsite-box PE-15, Volume SN-46)
- Arbitration Committee records. Bond book. October 1874-October 1881, 1874-1881 (Offsite-box PE-15, Volume SN-47)
- Arbitration Committee records. September 1875-February 1877, 1875-1877 (Offsite-box PE-19, Volume SN-48)
- Arbitration Committee records. April-November 1883 (Offsite-box PE-19, Volume SN-49)
- Arbitration Committee records. March 1892-December 1900, 1892-1900 (Offsite-box PE-21, Volume SN-50)
- Arbitration Committee records. Submissions. November 1881-February 1892, 1881-1892 (Offsite-box PE-20, Volume SN-51)
- Arbitration Committee records. June 1891-June 1892, 1891-1892 (Offsite-box PE-20, Volume SN-52)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1892-1893 (Offsite-box PE-21, Volume SN-53)
  When volumes SN-53 to SN-66 and SN-331 were inventoried in 2020, they were already shrinkwrapped for offsite storage so their date ranges could not be specifically determined, but the approximate ranges could be ascertained.
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1894-1895 (Offsite-box PE-22, Volume SN-54)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1896-1897 (Offsite-box PE-23, Volume SN-55)
- Arbitration Committee records, 1898-1899 (Offsite-box PE-24, Volume SN-56)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1899-1900 (Offsite-box PE-25, Volume SN-331)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1900-1901 (Offsite-box PE-26, Volume SN-57)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1902-1903 (Offsite-box PE-27, Volume SN-58)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1904-1905 (Offsite-box PE-28, Volume SN-59)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1906-1907 (Offsite-box PE-29, Volume SN-60)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1908-1909 (Offsite-box PE-30, Volume SN-61)
- Arbitration Committee records. December 1909-October 1911, 1909-1911 (Offsite-box PE-31, Volume SN-62)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1911-1912 (Offsite-box PE-32, Volume SN-63)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1912-1914 (Offsite-box PE-33, Volume SN-64)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1914-1915 (Offsite-box PE-34, Volume SN-65)
- Arbitration Committee records, circa 1915-1917 (Offsite-box PE-35, Volume SN-66)
- Arbitration Committee records. June 1917-May 1945, 1917-1945 (Offsite-box PE-36, Volume SN-67)
  This volume has relatively few and brief entries.
- Arbitration Committee records. Awards and agreements. September 1909-May 1916, 1909-1916 (Offsite-box PE-37, Volume SN-68)
- Arbitration Committee records. Awards and agreements, 1924-1934 (Offsite-box PE-37, Volume SN-69)
- Arbitration Committee records. Awards and agreements. March 1919-March 1924, 1919-1924 (Offsite-box PE-38, Volume SN-70)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. May 1919-July 1920, 1919-1920 (Offsite-box PE-38, Volume SN-71)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. July 1920-February 1921, 1920-1921 (Offsite-box PE-39, Volume SN-72)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. December 1921-July 1923, 1921-1923 (Offsite-box PE-39, Volume SN-73)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. July 1923-October 1925, 1923-1925 (Offsite-box PE-40, Volume SN-74)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. October 1925-July 1931, 1925-1931 (Offsite-box PE-41, Volume SN-75)
- Private Arbitration Committee. Awards and agreements. October 1931-April 1941, 1931-1941 (Offsite-box PE-42, Volume SN-76)
- W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Libellant) vs. James Richardson & Sons Ltd., et al. (Respondents), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-77)
- W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Libellant) vs. James Richardson & Sons Ltd., et al. (Respondents), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-78)
- W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Libellant) vs. James Richardson & Sons Ltd., et al. (Respondents), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-79)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-80)
  Volumes SN-80 to SN-89 are the originals and copies of Volumes 1 and 2 of the litigation transcript. See Box 1 for Volume 3.
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-81)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-16, Volume SN-82)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-17, Volume SN-83)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-17, Volume SN-84)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-17, Volume SN-85)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-17, Volume SN-86)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-18, Volume SN-87)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-18, Volume SN-88)
- James Richardson & Sons Ltd. (Cross-libellant) vs. W.E. Hedger Transportation Corp (Cross-Respondent), 1938 (Offsite-box PE-18, Volume SN-89)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 2. May 1872-June 1874, 1872-1874 (Offsite-box PE-43, Volume SN-90)
  See SN-189 for volume 1 (1861-1872).
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 3. June-December 1874 (Offsite-box PE-43, Volume SN-91)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 4. January-April 1875 (Offsite-box PE-43, Volume SN-92)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 5. May 1875-April 1876, 1875-1876 (Offsite-box PE-43, Volume SN-93)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 6. May 1876-February 1877, 1876-1877 (Offsite-box PE-44, Volume SN-94)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 7. March 1877-April 1878, 1877-1878 (Offsite-box PE-44, Volume SN-95)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume [8]. April-October 1878 (Offsite-box PE-44, Volume SN-96)
  The volume's spine incorrectly identifies this as volume 7.
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume [9]. October 1878-November 1879, 1878-1879 (Offsite-box PE-44, Volume SN-97)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume [10]. December 1879-December 1880, 1879-1880 (Offsite-box PE-45, Volume SN-98)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 11. January-October 1881 (Offsite-box PE-45, Volume SN-99)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 12. November 1881-November 1882, 1881-1882 (Offsite-box PE-45, Volume SN-100)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 13. November 1882-October 1883, 1882-1883 (Offsite-box PE-45, Volume SN-101)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 14. October 1883-October 1884, 1883-1884 (Offsite-box PE-46, Volume SN-102)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 15. October 1884-June 1885, 1884-1885 (Offsite-box PE-46, Volume SN-103)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 16. June 1885-May 1886, 1885-1886 (Offsite-box PE-46, Volume SN-104)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 17. May 1886-June 1887, 1886-1887 (Offsite-box PE-46, Volume SN-105)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume [18]. June 1887-June 1888, 1887-1888 (Offsite-box PE-47, Volume SN-106)
  The volume's spine incorrectly indicates this as volume 19.
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 19. July 1888-February 1890, 1888-1890 (Offsite-box PE-47, Volume SN-107)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 23a. October 1896-February 1897, 1896-1897 (Offsite-box PE-47, Volume SN-108)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 20. February 1890-March 1891, 1890-1891 (Offsite-box PE-47, Volume SN-109)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 21. July 1891-May 1893, 1891-1893 (Offsite-box PE-48, Volume SN-110)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 22. July 1893-June 1895, 1893-1895 (Offsite-box PE-48, Volume SN-111)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 23. June 1895-December 1896, 1895-1896 (Offsite-box PE-48, Volume SN-112)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 25. October 1898-October 1900, 1898-1900 (Offsite-box PE-49, Volume SN-113)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 24. December 1896-October 1898, 1896-1898 (Offsite-box PE-49, Volume SN-114)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 26. October 1900-October 1902, 1900-1902 (Offsite-box PE-49, Volume SN-115)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 27. October 1902-August 1904, 1902-1904 (Offsite-box PE-50, Volume SN-116)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 28. August 1904-August 1906, 1904-1906 (Offsite-box PE-50, Volume SN-117)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 29. August 1906-October 1908, 1906-1908 (Offsite-box PE-50, Volume SN-118)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 30. October 1908-March 1911, 1908-1911 (Offsite-box PE-51, Volume SN-119)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 31. April 1911-August 1914, 1911-1914 (Offsite-box PE-51, Volume SN-120)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 32. September 1914-June 1920, 1914-1920 (Offsite-box PE-51, Volume SN-121)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 33. June 1920-June 1924, 1920-1924 (Offsite-box PE-52, Volume SN-122)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 34. June 1924-August 1926, 1924-1926 (Offsite-box PE-52, Volume SN-123)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 35. September 1926-August 1929, 1926-1929 (Offsite-box PE-52, Volume SN-124)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 36. September 1929-August 1931, 1929-1931 (Offsite-box PE-53, Volume SN-125)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 37. August 1931-June 1934, 1931-1934 (Offsite-box PE-53, Volume SN-126)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 38. June 1934-December 1936, 1934-1936 (Offsite-box PE-53, Volume SN-127)
  See also Box 1 for the Board of Managers agendas and related correspondence and other supporting documents for the meetings of December 20, 1934, August 1, 1935, and January 2, 1936.
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 39. January 1937-June 1939, 1937-1939 (Offsite-box PE-54, Volume SN-128)
- Board of Managers minutes, Volume 40. June 1939-December 1941, 1939-1941 (Offsite-box PE-54, Volume SN-129)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. February 1871-April 1877, 1871-1877 (Offsite-box PE-54, Volume SN-130)
  Volumes SN-130 to SN-139 primarily hold minutes of the meetings of the exchange members. The volumes also hold the meeting minutes of various committees. The Grain Trade Committee appears most frequently. Others that appear, though not necessarily consistently through all the volumes, are the committees on provisions, butter, petroleum, flour, steamship trade, lard, and others.
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. December 1879-March 1883, 1879-1883 (Offsite-box PE-55, Volume SN-131)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. April 1877-December 1879, 1877-1879 (Offsite-box PE-55, Volume SN-132)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. April 1883-September 1884, 1883-1884 (Offsite-box PE-55, Volume SN-133)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. September 1884-January 1887, 1884-1887 (Offsite-box PE-55, Volume SN-134)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. January 1887-July 1891, 1887-1891 (Offsite-box PE-56, Volume SN-135)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. October 1891-December 1897, 1891-1897 (Offsite-box PE-56, Volume SN-136)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. January 1898-June 1902, 1898-1902 (Offsite-box PE-57, Volume SN-137)
- Member meeting and committee meeting minutes. June 1902-June 1907, 1902-1907 (Offsite-box PE-57, Volume SN-138)